WIKTORIA BIGAJ



07591384152



bigajwiktoria@gmail.com



wiktoriabigaj.tumblr.com



Hello! My name is Wiktoria and I am an Illustrator and a User Interface Designer, originally from Poland based in Belfast, Northern Ireland. I currently studying BDes (Hons) Interaction design at the Belfast School of Art. I have always been passionate about art since a very young age, and that is why I moved on to study what I love. I specialize in Illustration, Iconography Design and User Interface design. I am very confident in using Adobe Creative Suite, particularly Illustrator and Photoshop. I also code in HTML and CSS to craft digital experiences for the Internet. I love starting my work from simple paper sketches and taking them further digitally. I always push myself and my boundaries as a designer to get out of my comfort zone. I am looking forward to working in the design field with professionals to learn more and grow as a designer.



EDUCATION

2021 BDes (Hons) Interaction design - Belfast School of Art Grade: Pending 2017 BTEC Level 3 Foundation Diploma in Art and Design Grade: Distinction Southern Regional College 2016 BTEC Level 3 Diploma in Art and Design Grade: Distinction *, Distinction, Distinction Southern Regional College 2014

EXPERIENCE

September 2018- Ongoing Revolution de Cuba:

Working as waitress and a bartender.

Septemper 2017- September 2018 Build a Burger Belfast:

In Build a Burger Belfast the position I held was Front Crew staff/Deliveries. My responsibilities include costumer service, food preparation and till service. Costumer service is a massive part of my responsibilities, making sure that costumers experience is best it could be.

July 2017 – August 2017 Moy Park Food Company:

In Moy Park I have worked as a Production Operative. Working with raw and cooked food, making sure high standards of hygiene and safety were reached. Working with a larger group of people made me focus on my communication skills and team work. The communication between us was a key for successful production. Working with large masses of food made me focus on details.

JP's Tatsty Take Away:

Working in JP's Tasty for two years I have learned many core skills needed for all types of jobs. I have worked as; Front Crew Staff, working with the till, preparing, serving and packing food for costumers. I am well trained working under pressure and time management. I have learned how to work well as a part of a team for everything to go smoothly, we had to communicate well.

2018

2017

2015





